







Technical Lead-RPA seeking roles in Application Development, Application Support, Agile Methodology, Technical Documentation, Stakeholder Management, Project Management, Cloud Computing, Process Improvement, Python, Linux, SQL Server, Servicenow, Javascript



Total Experience: 10 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Notice Period: 3 Months

Current Designation: Technical Lead - RPA

Current Company: NA

Current Location: Navi Mumbai

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Canada, United

Kinadom (UK)

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Team Lead/Tech Lead

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Technical Lead-RPA, Team Lead/Tech Lead, Application Development, Application Support, Agile Methodology, Technical Documentation, Stakeholder Management, Project Management, Cloud Computing, Process

Improvement, Python, Linux, SQL Server, Servicenow, Javascript

Verified : Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 18-Jan-21 Last Modified: 18-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Certified IT Professional having 10+ years of experience of which 3+ years of experience as Lead RPA developer Over 6+ years of experience in application development, support, maintenance. Worked as a Business Analyst and Subject Matter Expert(SME) for migration projects

Successfully established RPA capabilities to justify its effectiveness as a tool which can considerably reduce the time and effort in comparison with a manual process

As a RPA Lead involved in functional /technical discussions, requirement reviews, process feasibilities (POC) and assessments, creation of process deliverables (VSR/ADD/SDD/checklist/runbook), onshore client communications, Bot process development, team mentoring

Having good knowledge of RPAlifecycle and automation projects delivery

Worked in Agile environment using Azure Dev-ops and executed sprint planning, daily scrum calls, impediment resolutions, tracking deliverables

Work Experience

- NA as Technical Lead RPA Aug 2013 to Till Date
- Hexaware Technologies as Software Developer Sep 2012 to Feb 2013
- Nexstep Infotech as Software Developer Jul 2009 to Aug 2012

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from University of Mumbai, Mumbai in 2008

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name Version Last Used Experience

Important

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Python, Linux, Regular Expressions	
API, VB Script, JavaScript	
SharePoint, SQLServer, AWSCloud	
AzureDev-ops,MSPowerPlatform	
ServiceNow, BMC	

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Marathi				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Category: **General**Physically Challenged: **No**

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.